SAI MOHAN B

bmohan048@gmai.com 7349159919 BTM 1st Stage Bengaluru, Karnataka

Summary

Highly effective software trainer has extensive knowledge of a wide variety of applications and operating systems commonly used in businesses. Stays constantly current with newly released applications and incorporates them into training materials. Has a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology terrific oral presentation skills with an outgoing and engaging personality and two years of experience as a Software Trainer.

Education

HIGH SCHOOL

Oxford English High School • Shivamogga, Karnataka

05/2012

SSC -84%

Board: Karnataka Secondary Education Examination Board

Pre-University Education

DVS Composite P.U College • Shimoga, Karnataka

05/2014

Computer Science-88%

Board: Department Of Pre-University Education

Graduation

Jawaharlal Nehru National College of Engineering • Shivamogga, Karnataka

06/2018

Presented the paper on "Artificial Intelligence In Cyber-Security" conducted on College Event

Techzone -2018

Graduated With -59%

Board: VTU University

Experience

Software Trainer

Ethnus • Bangalore, Karnataka

07/2018 - Present

Training - VIT University (Vellore campus 2018-2019)

- Conducting, assessing student's training via instructor-led training model through classroom-based languages such as java, python.
- Conducted the company-specific oriented training like SDOT, TCSDigital, TCS Ninja, Wipro, amazon in VIT University(Vellore as well as Chennai campus).

Skills

- C
- JavaScript
- React.js
- MYSQL

- Java
- Node.js
- PHP
- ORA

Languages

- English
- Kannada
- Telugu

- Hindi
- Tamil

Projects

Image Coupling using the Image Blending Techniques

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

Project description:

The composite image must consist of images placed at the right position and the aim is to make the edges between images invisible. The quality of blending is therefore expressed by measuring both the correspondence between adjacent stitched images that form the composite image and the visibility of the seam between the stitched images.

Login System Using PHP and MYSQL

This Project Consist of HTML5 ,CSS3 as the Front End and MYSQL as the Backend which is the complete login and Registration Form ,User Can enter the required Details Mentioned in the Form and the details Will be stored in the backend database Which will form a Complete Full Stacck APP

Hobbies

Traveling, Reading Books,